http://www.childrensalliance.org/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Image
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. We NEVER trade, sell or rent the contact information of our subscribers. Your home address is used to determine your elected officials by your district and to keep our internal records up to date.
Children's Alliance Privacy Statement
The following statement discloses the privacy practices for the Children's Alliance regarding electronic communications. Please direct any questions regarding this statement to seattle@childrensalliance.org.
We are committed to protecting your privacy. We only gather personal information from you via the Internet if you provide it voluntarily. We use this information to send you the electronic communications that you have requested. We may occasionally ask for your support for our child advocacy work. We maintain the privacy of your information using security technologies and adhere to policies that prevent unauthorized use of your personal information.
The following statement provides more details of our privacy practices.
Sender of Messages
We will only send you messages from the Children's Alliance.
Credit Card Security
The Children's Alliance is grateful for the donations we receive that help us to continue our work. It is important to us that any information you provide when making an online donation remains secure. Your credit card information is secured by a reputable security company. The information is used only for that particular transaction and is not stored.
Domain Name
Our Web server automatically recognizes, but does not collect or use, your domain name. The Children's Alliance anonymously tracks your visit in order to compile statistical information about the use of our website. We do not collect individual information about you or your use of this site.
Cookie Use
Cookies are pieces of information that are stored on your computer to help identify you while you visit our website. We use cookies to make visiting and using our website easier—so that you don't have to continually re-enter form information, and so that we can tailor your visit to your expressed preferences. We do not use cookies to
surreptitiously collect any personal information from your computer.
Email Addresses
Our website does not automatically recognize your email address. We collect the email addresses of those who communicate with us by email and on some of our webpages. We use email links to allow you to contact us directly with questions or comments. This information is used to respond directly to your questions or comments. We may also use your comments to improve our site and program. We may file the emails you send to follow up with you about your comments.
Personal Information
You do not have to provide any personal information unless you choose to do so. We do ask for personal information on our donations pages. We use this information to acknowledge receipt of your donation for tax purposes. In addition, your name and other information will be placed on our mailing list unless you chose to opt-out of receiving hard copy mailings. We will provide opt-out options at multiple locations. The content of letters you send to targets will only be accessible by the administrator at the Children's Alliance and will not be shared.
Opt-Out
This site gives you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving additional information from the Children's Alliance. If you do not want to receive additional information, please express your preferences on your Subscription Management page.
This site has links to other websites whose privacy policies may differ from ours. The Children's Alliance is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of organizations to which our websites are linked, but which are not partner organizations (Subscribe to partner organizations here).
Privacy Policy Changes
We reserve the right to change any of these policies in the future. Our current privacy policy will always be disclosed on this page; we encourage you to visit it often to stay abreast of any changes that may have been made. Your continued use of this website after the date that any changes are posted will be deemed as your agreement to the changed terms.
If you feel that your privacy has been violated or that we have misused your information in any way, please contact us.
Select LanguageEnglishAfrikaansAlbanianArabicArmenianAzerbaijaniBasqueBelarusianBengaliBosnianBulgarianCatalanCebuanoChinese (Simplified)Chinese (Traditional)CroatianCzechDanishDutchEsperantoEstonianFilipinoFinnishFrenchGalicianGeorgianGermanGreekGujaratiHaitian CreoleHausaHebrewHindiHmongHungarianIcelandicIgboIndonesianIrishItalianJapaneseJavaneseKannadaKhmerKoreanLaoLatinLatvianLithuanianMacedonianMalayMalteseMaoriMarathiMongolianNepaliNorwegianPersianPolishPortuguesePunjabiRomanianRussianSerbianSlovakSlovenianSomaliSpanishSwahiliSwedishTamilTeluguThaiTurkishUkrainianUrduVietnameseWelshYiddishYorubaZulu
© 2016 Children's Alliance
